BOLAJI OYEDELE



CONTACT

52 Lambo Lasunwon St, Ikorodu, IKORODU 104101, LA, Lagos, Lagos 104101 Nigeria

\(+2349025563043

SKILLS

- · Hardware and Software Engineering
- · Software development
- · Code debugging
- · Creative thinking
- · Product design
- Photoshop

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Insightful Engineering Technician with background collaborating with engineers and scientists on product development. Focused on supporting research and development, manufacturing and inspection processes through technical oversight and problem solving. Keen eye for detail when guiding testing and assisting with regulatory and certification processes.

EXPERIENCE

Self-employed | Lagos, Lagos

November 2020 - Current

Konica Minolta Bizhub Engineering

I repair and sell Konica Minolta bizhub printing machines to clients with whom I have built relationships to help them scale and build good relationships with their customers for a better printing ecosystem.

Amazing Grace | Lagos, Lagos

February 2019 - April 2020

Chief Engineer

I was responsible for heading a team of interns and attending to customers that requested our attention for their faulty machines.

· Presented technical resolution to address mechanical troubleshooting issues.

Amazing Grace Concept | Lagos, Lagos

November 2018 - November 2019

Engineering Intern

I worked as an intern to gain experience in repairing Bizhub colored printing machines.

Okeg | Ikorodu, Lagos

September 2016 - November 2017

Graphic Designer

I was responsible for attending to walk-in customers to create and design jobs to be printed or copied for other purposes.

EDUCATION

February 2023

Computer Software Engineering

ALX/Holberton Computer Science School, San Francisco, CA, United States

High School Diploma - Art and Science Ikorodu High School, Ikorodu , Lagos

LANGUAGES

English

Fluent

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Swimming
- Gaming
- Coding